Matthew R Green

MatthewRGreen01@Gmail.com 465 West 148th Street Apt. 4A New York, NY 10031 954 - 290 - 2619

Summary

Current Hunter student majoring in computer science. Experienced in exceptional customer service. Proved to be an outstanding team leader at Jamba Juice, and am presently working for fairway market. I am confident in my ability to prioritize, multitask, and work in a fast paced high pressure environment.

Education

Hunter College 2014 - Present

Major: Computer Science Graduation date: Spring 2018

Work Experience

Fairway Market: E-Commerce 2328 12th Ave, New York, NY 10027

2016 - Present

- Collected and prepared items for transactions conducted electronically
- Assisted customers to select merchandise based on their preferences and needs
- Handled inventory and reviewed merchandise movement
- Carefully followed directions customers put on their order for requested items

Jamba Juice: Management 95 East Houston Street, New York, NY 10002 2014 - 2015

- Supervised a fast paced and high pressure environment
- Worked as a member of a team to promote a positive experience for employees
- Trained up to 20 employees in transaction protocols and customer relations
- Provided superior customer service and resolved customer complaints
- Managed stock with meticulous record keeping and organization
- Responsible for accounting, book-keeping, office operation, and accountability